Mehul Vardiya

Systems Engineer

I describe as a hardworking professional having experience in working with Full Stack Developer. I am a fast learner and open to working in any technical field. I can use artistic and creative skills to work for the future success and betterment of the organization.

Work History

2021-11 -Current

Systems Engineer

Infosys, Jaipur

- In company project worked as "Engineering Solution Delivery".
- Worked on MERN Stack Development.

2019-06 -2019-07

Training

Hornet Dynamics Pvt. Ltd, Jaipur

 Worked in Full Stack Development and various technologies including HTML, CSS, Bootstrap 4, Java Script.

Education

2017-08 -20210

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY: COMPUTER SCIENCE & ENGINEERING

Arya College Of Engineering & Research Centre -Jaipur, Rajasthan

Certifications

- Front-End Web UI Frameworks and Tools: Bootstrap 4 (Affiliated by Coursera)
- Web Design for Everybody: Basics of Web Development & Coding (Affiliated by Coursera)

Projects

OMNIFOOD BRAND WEBSITE: This Website offers user to view different food plans.

RISTORANTE CON FUSION: This website offers user to booking online restaurant table and view online menu.



Contact

Address

Banswara, 327001

Phone

7665963178

E-mail

vardiyamehul@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mehul-vardiya-6a52111

Technical Profile

- C++
- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- Node.js
- React.is
- GitHub

Interests

Travelling